

Grant Hardison

Responsible Airport Assistant Manager with 10+ years of experience overseeing operations in small and major airports. Effective negotiator and proactive leader with strong analytical and planning skills. Enjoys investing knowledge and confidence into others and promoting excellent customer service and excuse-free compliance.

Professional Experience

Assistant Airport Manager

Boston Logan International Airport, Boston, MA January 2016- Present

- Training employees on customer service, confrontation avoidance, and compliance, resultingin 30% fewer negative customer interactions in 2018 and 2019
- Helping ensure compliance with company, airport, and FAA regulations and policies
- Working with the airport manager to set up training schedules for employees
- Helping the airport manager negotiate contracts with vendors, saving the airport
 25% in office supply costs and over \$2 million in food service-related costs

Senior Assistant to Airport Manager

Shenandoah Valley Regional Airport, Weyers Cave, VA December 2010 - November 2015

- Assisted airport manager in short- and long-term planning and marketing of airport services, securing five new vendors
- Helped prepare budgets, oversaw capital projects and maintained leases with tenants, cutting capital overhead costs by 14% between 2012-2015
- Prepared reports of daily a irport operation s
- Responded to aircraft emergencies, averted a runway crash in 2011

Airport Operations Coordinator

Shenandoah Valley Regional Airport, Weyers Cave, VA October 2008 - December 2010

- Ensured safe, efficient flow of passengers throughout terminals
- ♦ In s pected a i rpo rt fac i l iti es for sa fety com pl ia n ce
- ♦ Hei ped d e vise a nd i mp lem e nt a i rpo rt em e rgency pla n

3859 Victory Avenue, Braintree, MA 02184 ghardy20@email,conn (774) 123-0000

Education

Associate of Applied Science in Aviation Maintenance Technology Blue Ridge Community College, Weyers Cave, VA January 2013- December 2015

Key Skills

- Leadership
- Verbal and written communication
- Negotiation
- High familiarity with security regulations